Let's see what you missed this week in the Amandaverse.
Y'all, this is a very big deal.
Scientists successfully produced a nuclear fusion reaction
resulting in a net energy gain.
This is big for science.
This is big for all of us.
This article said more than 55% of people
aren't honest on their resumes.
Okay, SEAL squad,
are y'all keeping it a buck on your resumes?
I would love in the comments
if y'all would share some of the lies that you may have used
or that a friend, maybe it's a friend,
may have used on their resume in the past.
Each one, teach one.
Can we just dump the dad sneaker?
Please, for 2023, I'm tired.
I'm somebody that wears a size nine and a half, y'all,
and I got flat feet.
I got enough of a dad sneaker built into my anatomy
for y'all to then put one on top of it.
What's the toast?
To the motherland?
So we're at the Alafia compound.
Y'all, I was in the heart of it, okay?
We was making the shea butter from scratch.
I got to see more of the country,
taking some roadside beer.
We even went on a mini little safari.
I'm coming in the day of a buck.